What I didn't realize is all these three
events that I'm about to rattle off all
happened within 5 days of each other.
So, February 11th, 2011, Yonkers video
premieres.
>> [music]
>> Pretty much overnight viral sensation.
Within weeks, Kanye's tweeting it's the
best music video of the year. It's
getting rotation on MTV. Three days
later, Tyler signs a one album deal with
XL. Yonkers officially released as a
single. Two days after that, they're on
Late Night with Jimmy Fallon.
So, the team and Hodgy just going crazy.
Tyler's got the green ski mask on. He's
jumping around. At some point, he runs
off stage and goes to the guests and
like shakes the guests up. You remember
the lady with the long hair just like on
stage going like this like super creepy?
>> And I also remember, this is weird,
Tyler jumps on Jimmy Fallon's back, a
very LIKE ICONIC MOMENT.
>> [cheering]
>> TWO ICONIC THINGS WITHIN 5 days. And
then Tyler's just like
>> to the moon.
>> to the moon. Also, coincidentally, same
day as that performance, Frank Ocean
releases Nostalgia Ultra.